Dykyi Vladyslav

Front-End developer

■ dykyiovladyslav@gmail.com • Ukraine Dnipro • @wildmagictv in Linkedin

SUMMARY

I have 4 years of site development, of which: 3 years of experience in designing sites for different devices, and technologies for displaying the UI part of the site, and 1 year of working with JavaScript, the React.js and Next.js framework, for creating a high-quality site.

TECH SKILLS

- HTML / CSS / SCSS / SASS
- Bootstrap 3 / 4 / 5
- JavaScript / ES6+ / Luxon
- React / Router / Redux / Formik / RTK / RTK Query / MUI 5+ / I18next
- Git Hub / npm / Gulp / Vite / API / Storybook
- Figma / PhotoShop

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Startup 01/2024 - present

Front-End

- Front-End development
- Code review
- Communication with the Back-End, Design and QA team
- Bescription of tasks
- Teamwork
- Help and mentoring

Core Technologies: React / MUI 5+ / I18next / Formik / Yup / Redux / Router / RTK /

RTK Query / Luxon / Storybook

Hillel IT School 09/2021 - present Teaching programming to teenagers, namely: Dnipro, Ukraine

• Teaching students how to code right

- Code review
- Publick speaking
- Managing tasks between students

Core technologies: HTML / CSS / JavaScript

WebGenerator 04/2021 - 09/2023 Front-End Dnipro, Ukraine

- Front-End development
- Communication with the project client / Back-End developers / Designers
- Code review
- Teamwork
- Assessment of the project and tasks

Core Technologies: HTML / SCSS / Bootstrap / Gulp / JavaScript / React

Freelance 10/2021 - 05/2022

Font-End

- Front-End development
- Comunication with the prodject client / Back-End / Designer
- Code review

Core Technologies: HTML / SCSS / Bootstrap 3 - 4 / Gulp / Jquery / JavaScript

EDUCATION

Electrical energetics, electrical engineering and electromichanics

COURSES

Hillel IT School	11/2020 – 03/2021
Front-End pro	Dnipro, Ukraine
Hillel IT School Front-End basic HTML / CSS	07/2020 – 11/2020 Dnipro, Ukraine
Hillel IT School	03/2021 – 06/2021
React	Dnipro, Ukraine

SOFT SKILLS

- Comunications
- Critical thinking
- Teamwork
- Attention to detail
- Solving problemsWork ethic

LANGUAGES

English Ukrainian Pre-Intermediate Native